[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 4, "question": "Now can he help me with my game?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "can", "he", "help", "me", "with", "my", "game", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 5, "answer": "I'll do what I can, but I can't work miracles.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "do", "what", "I", "can", ",", "but", "I", "ca", "n't", "work", "miracles", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["95 percent"]}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "When it actually comes down to it, when you're entering that fourth day as you did, what is it that makes a champion compared to others who often fall by the wayside?", "question_tokens": ["When", "it", "actually", "comes", "down", "to", "it", ",", "when", "you", "'re", "entering", "that", "fourth", "day", "as", "you", "did", ",", "what", "is", "it", "that", "makes", "a", "champion", "compared", "to", "others", "who", "often", "fall", "by", "the", "wayside", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Yes, I mean -- I mean think I know more than anyone else from this year's Masters, you know, what happened to me, it's, you know, 95 percent of it is mental.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", "--", "I", "mean", "think", "I", "know", "more", "than", "anyone", "else", "from", "this", "year", "'s", "Masters", ",", "you", "know", ",", "what", "happened", "to", "me", ",", "it", "'s", ",", "you", "know", ",", "95", "percent", "of", "it", "is", "mental", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "How did they react to this young whippersnapper from Ireland coming in and winning their trophy?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "they", "react", "to", "this", "young", "whippersnapper", "from", "Ireland", "coming", "in", "and", "winning", "their", "trophy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "You know I felt as if the reception I got from the American people was very good.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "I", "felt", "as", "if", "the", "reception", "I", "got", "from", "the", "American", "people", "was", "very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ireland"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "How did your dad react to this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "your", "dad", "react", "to", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "He was fantastic all week.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "fantastic", "all", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Guinness"]}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "Now which is it?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "which", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Never Guinness.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "Guinness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Never Guinness?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "Guinness", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "You don't like Guinness?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "like", "Guinness", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "No, I'm not -- I'm not a big fan.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "a", "big", "fan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Guinness"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "For a young man growing up as you did there, what was it like for you?", "question_tokens": ["For", "a", "young", "man", "growing", "up", "as", "you", "did", "there", ",", "what", "was", "it", "like", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "You know, personally I've never seen the violence.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "personally", "I", "'ve", "never", "seen", "the", "violence", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Do you feel that the weight of the expectation of the Irish on your shoulders?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "the", "weight", "of", "the", "expectation", "of", "the", "Irish", "on", "your", "shoulders", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "A little bit, but I don't mind that.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "bit", ",", "but", "I", "do", "n't", "mind", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Or can you be both?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "can", "you", "be", "both", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "It's hard.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "That's probably the diplomatic answer, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "probably", "the", "diplomatic", "answer", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Did you have a tough upbringing, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "a", "tough", "upbringing", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "What did they do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "they", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "My dad was a bar manager and worked in separate places, you know, in the daytime and then in the night.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "dad", "was", "a", "bar", "manager", "and", "worked", "in", "separate", "places", ",", "you", "know", ",", "in", "the", "daytime", "and", "then", "in", "the", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "It's been worth it, though, hasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "worth", "it", ",", "though", ",", "has", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "PRP", ",", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Did you ever imagine when you were growing up and the other Hollywood, that the real one, one day would be a place that would welcome you like a conquering hero?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "when", "you", "were", "growing", "up", "and", "the", "other", "Hollywood", ",", "that", "the", "real", "one", ",", "one", "day", "would", "be", "a", "place", "that", "would", "welcome", "you", "like", "a", "conquering", "hero", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "CD", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Yes, it's --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "Pretty surreal, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Pretty", "surreal", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "It must have turned things upside down, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "must", "have", "turned", "things", "upside", "down", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Yes, it's -- I mean -- I didn't realize how much attention and focus was going to be on me after that.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "--", "I", "mean", "--", "I", "did", "n't", "realize", "how", "much", "attention", "and", "focus", "was", "going", "to", "be", "on", "me", "after", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Is it exciting or slightly terrifying?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "exciting", "or", "slightly", "terrifying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "CILROY: No, it's exciting.", "answer_tokens": ["CILROY", ":", "No", ",", "it", "'s", "exciting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "How have they reacted, the guys who've never won and tried for so long to do so?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "they", "reacted", ",", "the", "guys", "who", "'ve", "never", "won", "and", "tried", "for", "so", "long", "to", "do", "so", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "They've been very positive.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'ve", "been", "very", "positive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "CD", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "CD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Do you see any parallels with Tiger in terms of the way you play?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "see", "any", "parallels", "with", "Tiger", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "way", "you", "play", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "Yes, I mean, you know, at 22 we both had one major.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "know", ",", "at", "22", "we", "both", "had", "one", "major", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tiger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "That's a lot of pressure, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "pressure", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "It's part of the thing in sports to not be in awe of people?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "part", "of", "the", "thing", "in", "sports", "to", "not", "be", "in", "awe", "of", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Do you think you have the strength of character to deal with it in a way that Tiger ultimately turned out not to have?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "have", "the", "strength", "of", "character", "to", "deal", "with", "it", "in", "a", "way", "that", "Tiger", "ultimately", "turned", "out", "not", "to", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "I hope so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "It's not -- it's not a healthy way to live for relationships and stuff, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "--", "it", "'s", "not", "a", "healthy", "way", "to", "live", "for", "relationships", "and", "stuff", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "No, it's not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "What does she make of what's happening to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "she", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "happening", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "She -- I mean -- I think in a way it's tough on her.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "--", "I", "mean", "--", "I", "think", "in", "a", "way", "it", "'s", "tough", "on", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think wedding bells on the horizon here?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Do", "you", "think", "wedding", "bells", "on", "the", "horizon", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "No, not at the moment.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "the", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Does it depend on how good a degree she gets?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "depend", "on", "how", "good", "a", "degree", "she", "gets", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "I mean even with him, you want to kill him, right, on the golf course?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "even", "with", "him", ",", "you", "want", "to", "kill", "him", ",", "right", ",", "on", "the", "golf", "course", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "Where have you got that from?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "have", "you", "got", "that", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "I think you need that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "need", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "I mean if you tried to go home to Holly and the two dogs with the swagger and the arrogance and the cockiness, how would she react?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "if", "you", "tried", "to", "go", "home", "to", "Holly", "and", "the", "two", "dogs", "with", "the", "swagger", "and", "the", "arrogance", "and", "the", "cockiness", ",", "how", "would", "she", "react", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Probably with a slap from the back of her right hand.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "with", "a", "slap", "from", "the", "back", "of", "her", "right", "hand", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Holly"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Who's most inspired you?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "most", "inspired", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJS", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "I think for any golfer from my generation, watching Tiger -- you know growing up and winning his major championships was a huge inspiration for me to believe that, you know, maybe one day I could go on to emulate what he's done.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "for", "any", "golfer", "from", "my", "generation", ",", "watching", "Tiger", "--", "you", "know", "growing", "up", "and", "winning", "his", "major", "championships", "was", "a", "huge", "inspiration", "for", "me", "to", "believe", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "maybe", "one", "day", "I", "could", "go", "on", "to", "emulate", "what", "he", "'s", "done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Did he call you after the U.S. Open?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "call", "you", "after", "the", "U.S.", "Open", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "No, he left a message in the media center.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "left", "a", "message", "in", "the", "media", "center", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Saying what?", "question_tokens": ["Saying", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Just well done, great performance from start to finish.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "well", "done", ",", "great", "performance", "from", "start", "to", "finish", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "And not that well known in America, but in terms of his leadership, is he someone that inspires you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "not", "that", "well", "known", "in", "America", ",", "but", "in", "terms", "of", "his", "leadership", ",", "is", "he", "someone", "that", "inspires", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Yes, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "CC", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Did you sink into a kind of temporary oblivion of despair?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "sink", "into", "a", "kind", "of", "temporary", "oblivion", "of", "despair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "No, if anything it made me more determined to go back and to prove to a lot of people, not just the media but you know just everyone and prove to myself as well that I wasn't this person that they were making me out to be in the press, you know, a choker or you know can't handle the pressure.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "if", "anything", "it", "made", "me", "more", "determined", "to", "go", "back", "and", "to", "prove", "to", "a", "lot", "of", "people", ",", "not", "just", "the", "media", "but", "you", "know", "just", "everyone", "and", "prove", "to", "myself", "as", "well", "that", "I", "was", "n't", "this", "person", "that", "they", "were", "making", "me", "out", "to", "be", "in", "the", "press", ",", "you", "know", ",", "a", "choker", "or", "you", "know", "ca", "n't", "handle", "the", "pressure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Can you relax?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "relax", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "A little bit, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "bit", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "What was the best escape route for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "best", "escape", "route", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "I think to go and watch other sports -- sporting event.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "to", "go", "and", "watch", "other", "sports", "--", "sporting", "event", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Do you ever read books?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "read", "books", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Music -- do you listen to music?", "question_tokens": ["Music", "--", "do", "you", "listen", "to", "music", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Yes, music.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "music", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Swedish House Mafia"], "PERSON": ["David Guetta"]}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "What's on your iPod?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "on", "your", "iPod", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "I lot of -- lot of dancy, sort of techno, Swedish House Mafia, David Guetta.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "lot", "of", "--", "lot", "of", "dancy", ",", "sort", "of", "techno", ",", "Swedish", "House", "Mafia", ",", "David", "Guetta", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "All that sort of stuff, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "that", "sort", "of", "stuff", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", ":", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "What's the big ambition for you, personally and professionally?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "big", "ambition", "for", "you", ",", "personally", "and", "professionally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Personally, not to let all this attention that I'm going to probably get -- not let that affect me in any way.", "answer_tokens": ["Personally", ",", "not", "to", "let", "all", "this", "attention", "that", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "probably", "get", "--", "not", "let", "that", "affect", "me", "in", "any", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "The best golfer in history?", "question_tokens": ["The", "best", "golfer", "in", "history", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Is that now attainable to you, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "now", "attainable", "to", "you", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "I would probably be --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "probably", "be", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Did you throw the ball to me?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "throw", "the", "ball", "to", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Probably.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'61"]}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "-NONE-", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "I've gone every single year since '61.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "gone", "every", "single", "year", "since", "'61", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Do you still play tennis?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "play", "tennis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "ING: Well, I got to a point -- because I started having my first knee operation when I was 23 and I was number one in the world.", "answer_tokens": ["ING", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "got", "to", "a", "point", "--", "because", "I", "started", "having", "my", "first", "knee", "operation", "when", "I", "was", "23", "and", "I", "was", "number", "one", "in", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "How many surgeries have you had now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "surgeries", "have", "you", "had", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "I've had eight altogether on my knees.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "had", "eight", "altogether", "on", "my", "knees", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Central Park", "New York City"]}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "It's really worked?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "really", "worked", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "I just played tennis the last two days out in Central Park in New York City.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "played", "tennis", "the", "last", "two", "days", "out", "in", "Central", "Park", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Are you good these days?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "good", "these", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "No, I'm terrible.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "terrible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan"]}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "What were you thinking when that happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "thinking", "when", "that", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "When I found out, I was in Japan.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "found", "out", ",", "I", "was", "in", "Japan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret"]}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Because you had to shut him up, right?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "had", "to", "shut", "him", "up", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "So Margaret took one for the team by losing.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "Margaret", "took", "one", "for", "the", "team", "by", "losing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "ORGAN: When you beat him, how did that moment feel?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "When", "you", "beat", "him", ",", "how", "did", "that", "moment", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Such relief, thank you, God.", "answer_tokens": ["Such", "relief", ",", "thank", "you", ",", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PDT", "CC", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "When you went out afterwards, what was the reaction from women in particular to what you'd done?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "went", "out", "afterwards", ",", "what", "was", "the", "reaction", "from", "women", "in", "particular", "to", "what", "you", "'d", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I'd actually get half and half.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "actually", "get", "half", "and", "half", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Influenced him to do what?", "question_tokens": ["Influenced", "him", "to", "do", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Just to really think about always making sure his daughters or girls and women have opportunities just like boys.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "to", "really", "think", "about", "always", "making", "sure", "his", "daughters", "or", "girls", "and", "women", "have", "opportunities", "just", "like", "boys", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Did something happen to spark that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "something", "happen", "to", "spark", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "I think it's because I got into tennis when I was 11.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "because", "I", "got", "into", "tennis", "when", "I", "was", "11", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "That in itself created shock waves, didn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "in", "itself", "created", "shock", "waves", ",", "did", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "It did.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Yes, which I thought was a great compliment.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "which", "I", "thought", "was", "a", "great", "compliment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "What was the hardest barrier for you to break down, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "hardest", "barrier", "for", "you", "to", "break", "down", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "I think for me, probably being gay, being a lesbian.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "for", "me", ",", "probably", "being", "gay", ",", "being", "a", "lesbian", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "From what, endorsements?", "question_tokens": ["From", "what", ",", "endorsements", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Endorsements went bye-bye in 24 hours.", "answer_tokens": ["Endorsements", "went", "bye-bye", "in", "24", "hours", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "Looking back on it, did its actually make your life better in the longer terms?", "question_tokens": ["Looking", "back", "on", "it", ",", "did", "its", "actually", "make", "your", "life", "better", "in", "the", "longer", "terms", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP$", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "In the long run, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "the", "long", "run", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "Why would you advise other people not to come out?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "advise", "other", "people", "not", "to", "come", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "Because it's not right.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "it", "'s", "not", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "Have you stayed friends with Elton?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "stayed", "friends", "with", "Elton", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "Forever.", "answer_tokens": ["Forever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Have you seen his new baby yet?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "seen", "his", "new", "baby", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "How would you have got on against women who are so physically powerful?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "have", "got", "on", "against", "women", "who", "are", "so", "physically", "powerful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "This generation is so much better.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "generation", "is", "so", "much", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "What's been the greatest moment of your life?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "greatest", "moment", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "you're really asking difficult questions, because it depends.", "answer_tokens": ["you", "'re", "really", "asking", "difficult", "questions", ",", "because", "it", "depends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110630pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 729, "question": "Does anything beat the first one?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "anything", "beat", "the", "first", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 730, "answer": "Actually not.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]